

FRONT-END DEVELOPER AT TRIPMEDIC

angelcj.bcn@gmail.com angelcj.github.io Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain

Experience

Front-end developer TripMedic

Sep 2018 - Present Barcelona Area, Spain

Lead front-end developer inMotion Real Estate Media

Aug 2016 - Aug 2018 Barcelona Area, Spain

Freelance front-end developer & designer Freelance Web Developer

Sep 2015 - Jul 2016 Barcelona Area, Spain

Front-end developer and designer Klimber Tech

Mar 2015 - Sep 2015 Barcelona Area, Spain

Front-end developer ganesha produccions

Mar 2014 - Jan 2015 Barcelona Area, Spain

Education

Multiplatform App Development Computer Software Engineering

Institut Obert de Catalunya 2013 - 2015

Degree in Sociology Sociology

Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona 2010 - 2014

Skills

HTML5, CSS, SASS, SEO, Web Development, Web Applications, User Experience, Front-end Development, Search Engine Optimization (SEO), Usability, JavaScript, jQuery, Github, Git, Bootstrap, WordPress, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), HTML, APIs, Gulp.js, npm, PSD to Wordpress, LESS

Languages

Catalan Native or bilingual

English Full professional

Spanish Native or bilingual

Profile

I'm a front-end developer with experience in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, WordPress, usability and cross-browser compatibility.

I've created a wide range of websites and small webapps working for various companies, as well as a freelance developer.

While I consider myself a front-end only developer, I have some experience with PHP (WordPress theme and plugin development) and MySQL, as well as setting up servers.

I'm also quite competent with Photoshop and Sketch, but I'm not a graphics designer, so you shouldn't count on me for creating your company logo.

These are some of my skills and qualities:

- HTML5, CSS3 and preprocessors such as LESS and SASS.
- Experience with CSS frameworks such as Bootstrap, Foundation, Bulma, Tychons and UIKit.
- JavaScript (ES5 and ES6) with and without jQuery. Some experience with Vue and React.
- Wordpress theme and pluging building form scratch, therefore, PHP, but nnot as a backend developer.
- Template engines such as Pug, EJS and Twig.
- Webpack and Gulp
- Versioning tools Git/VN.
- Clean code, Usability and Accessibility.
- Cross-browser, mobile-first websites and webapps.